dealncodes.com 2013-11-18

# Privacy Policy

What information does OnlineCouponIsland.com collect?

•             How does OnlineCouponIsland.com use the information they collect?

•             Does OnlineCouponIsland.com share my information?

•             What about the websites OnlineCouponIsland.com links to?

•             What are cookies, log files and web beacons?

•             What security precautions does OnlineCouponIsland.com take?

•             What are the Terms of Use?

•             Is there an age requirement to use OnlineCouponIsland.com?

•             What if I'm an international user?

•             How can I communicate with OnlineCouponIsland.com?

•             What if I have questions or comments?

1\. We collect personally identifiable information that is voluntarily provided by users like names, email addresses, and home addresses

2\. We collect non-personally identifiable information that is automatically collected like IP addresses and the type of web browser you are using

If you do not want personally identifiable information to be collected, do not submit it.

If you choose to become a registered member of OnlineCouponIsland.com, you will be required to submit a valid email address and create a password for your account. In the event that you want to close your account and remove your information from the OnlineCouponIsland.com service, please send your request to help@OnlineCouponIsland.com.

1\. Our primary goal is to enhance your experience on the OnlineCouponIsland.com website

a. This information may be used to provide technical support, enforce Terms of Use, communicate with users, develop display content and advertising tailored to your interests, or to manage our business operations

b. Information may be used for other functions that will be described to you at the time of collection

c. Information may be collected for third-party aggregate data. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information

2\. Non-personally identifiable information collected by OnlineCouponIsland.com is exclusively owned by OnlineCouponIsland.com.

1\. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third-parties for marketing purposes without your permission

2\. If required by law, OnlineCouponIsland.com will disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally identifiable information

3\. OnlineCouponIsland.com reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally identifiable information that OnlineCouponIsland.com believe is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of OnlineCouponIsland.com, our members or others

4\. We may share non-personally identifiable information with advertisers, business affiliates, publishers, and other third parties for marketing purposes

a. If you wish to be excluded from aggregate research, please email customer service at help@OnlineCouponIsland.com

5\. OnlineCouponIsland.com is not responsible for any information you choose to share with others

6\. In the event of that OnlineCouponIsland.com is merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our user and members as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control

7\. In the unlikely event of bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used

When clicking on coupon codes or other links to merchants, you will be sent via a new Web browser window. Third-party websites may also collect information from you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This privacy statement applied only to information collection on OnlineCouponIsland.com.

1\. Cookies are tiny data files which reside on your computer and allow OnlineCouponIsland.com to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser.

a. Like most websites, OnlineCouponIsland.com uses cookies and web log files to track site usage

b. Cookies do not store personally identifiable information

c. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser settings to decline cookies. In the event that you decline cookies it may affect the function of some interactive features on our website

2\. Log files store various non-personally identifiable data regarding your visit such as internet protocol address (IP address), information about your browser, internet service provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring and exit pages, platform type, and number of and identification of clicks.

a. Most websites use log files as part of the Internet communication standards

b. This information is used to analyze overall trends, diagnose problems with our server, or display content according to your preferences

c. This anonymous information may be shared with business partners and advertisers on a aggregate and anonymous basis

3\. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier that function similar to cookies, and are used to track online movement of web users or to access cookies.

a. Web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages

b. This information is used to track user navigation and usage patterns, and to show us if our content and communication is effective

e. Web beacons do not store personally identifiable information

f. This information may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads

1\. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall

No method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to OnlineCouponIsland.com and you do so at your own risk.

2\. It is your responsibility to keep your password confidential

3\. In the event of a security breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate proactive steps

a. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive this notice in writing please email help@OnlineCouponIsland.com

4\. If you have questions about the security of OnlineCouponIsland.com, please see our Security Response page

If you choose to visit OnlineCouponIsland.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, and application of law of the state of Texas. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications to our Privacy Policy will take effect immediately, and material changes to our Privacy Policy will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. We will post a new or changed policy's effective date. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

Is there an age requirement to use OnlineCouponIsland.com?

1\. No one under the age of 18 is eligible to use our services

2\. We do not direct any of our content specifically at children under the age of 18

3\. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 18

4\. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age

18, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.

a. If you believe that we may have information from or about a child under 18, please contact us at help@OnlineCouponIsland.com

If you access OnlineCouponIsland.com from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differs from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the OnlineCouponIsland.com website and services, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you are expressly consenting to that transfer, and our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

1\. OnlineCouponIsland.com will communicate with you through emails and notices posted on the OnlineCouponIsland.com website

a. You will always receive emails that relate to the proper function of your account

b. OnlineCouponIsland.com may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information

2\. If you wish to stop receiving emails, please send a request to help@OnlineCouponIsland.com

Please email support@OnlineCouponIsland.com or contact us at:

2275 Lakeshore Blvd., W

Toronto, Ontario M8V 3Y3

Toronto

Ontario,2275

Attn: Online Coupon Island Customer Support
